1-Atoms/icons/close@3x
    
    * Who We Are
        ==========

    * Who We Are
        ----------

    * Our Commitments
        ---------------

    * Learn More
        ----------

    1-Atoms/icons/close@3x
    
    * Our Impact
        ==========

    * Sustainability
        --------------

    * Diversity
        ---------

    * Community
        ---------

    1-Atoms/icons/close@3x
    
    * Our Brands
        ==========

    * Creating Smiles
        ---------------
        
    * [PepsiCo Health and Nutrition Sciences1-Atoms/icons/minus/black Copy@3x](https://pepsicohealthandnutritionsciences.com/)
    
    * For Shoppers
        ------------

    * For Business
        ------------

    1-Atoms/icons/close@3x
    
    * Resources
        =========

        * [PepsiCo Health and Nutrition SciencesPepsiCo Health and Nutrition Sciences](https://pepsicohealthandnutritionsciences.com/)

Privacy
=======

Welcome to the PepsiCo, Inc. ("PepsiCo") website. Below you will find our Privacy Notice regarding any personal information that you may supply to us through this website.

### PEPSICO PRIVACY NOTICE

##### June 30, 2024

It is our aim through this **PEPSICO UNITED STATES PRIVACY NOTICE (“Notice”)** to explain what information we collect about you and why we collect that information. We also want to make sure you understand how we use and share your information and the choices available to you. Our goal is to earn and keep your trust as you visit websites and applications about our products and brands.

This Notice describes how we treat personal information on websites (“sites”), mobile or social media applications (“apps”), and any other services where we include an authorized link or reference to this Notice (together, the “Services”). This Notice does not describe our practices on sites or apps where it is not referenced.

Your use of our apps and sites indicates you agree to our collection, use, and sharing of your information as set forth in this Notice.

##### What information do we collect?

**We collect identifiers and contact information.** For example, we may collect your name and street address if you register on our site or apps. We may also collect your phone number or email address. We also collect online identifiers. For example, if you engage with us through a social media site, we may collect your social media user identifier.

**We collect payment information.** If you make purchases with us, we (or our business partners who process payment cards for us) may collect your billing information. This includes your payment card number.

**We collect information you submit or otherwise provide or authorize us to collect.** We collect the information you post in a public space on our site. This includes comments and videos or photos. We also collect any other information you may provide to us or authorize us to collect. This may include information about your physical activities or your nutrition preferences.

**We collect demographic information and information about your interests.** We may collect information such as your gender and age, household or lifestyle information, and your zip code.

**We collect internet and electronic network activity information, such as device and usage information.** We may collect information about the browser you are using, and we may look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us. We may also collect information about your operating system, Internet Service Provider (ISP) information and IP addresses and other device identifiers, such as mobile device identifiers. In addition, we may collect information about your use of our Services, including through use of tracking technologies such as cookies, pixel tags, and similar technologies. For additional information, please visit our [About Our Ads](https://www.pepsico.com/legal/about-our-ads) policy.

**We collect geolocation information.** Using technologies such as GPS or Wi-Fi, we may collect information about your location. For example, if you use our mobile apps, we may access your device’s location information to provide you location-enabled features.

**We collect job application information, such as professional or employment-related information and education information.** We collect information if you apply for a job with us. This information may include your education and work history, your skills, and qualifications for the position. We may ask about how you learned about the position. If applicable, we may ask about your driving record and your ability to perform the position. We may also collect the last four digits of your social security number and your nationality.

**We collect information about third parties.** From time to time, we may allow you to send an email or message to a friend through one of our sites or apps. If you choose to do this, we will need that person’s name and email address.

##### How do we collect information?

We collect information directly from you. We collect information from you when you:

* Make a purchase with us.
* Register on one of our sites or apps.
* Join our loyalty programs.
* Apply for a job.
* Sign up for our email newsletters and other notifications.
* Participate in promotions such as sweepstakes or contests.
* Fill out a survey. 
* Contact us.
* Physically visit one of our site locations.
* Otherwise submit it to us.

**We collect information from you passively.** We use tracking tools like browser cookies and mobile device IDs. We do this on our websites, in emails that we send to you, and in media advertising. We collect information about usage and browser information over time. We may have third parties collect personal information this way. We also collect information about you from our mobile apps.

**Third parties may also share information about you with us.** For example, our business partners may give us information about you. We may receive information from companies who compile information about shoppers and their preferences. Social media platforms may also give us information about you, and we may get information about your interactions with our ads on third-party sites.

##### We may combine information from different sources

**We may combine information.** For example, we may combine information we have collected offline with information we collect online. We combine information we have collected across third-party sites, including social media sites. We combine information across devices such as computers and mobile devices. We may also combine information from third parties with information we already have.  

##### How we may use the information we collect

**We may use information to help us effectively provide you products and services.** We use your information to respond to your questions or enable you to participate in our programs. This may include sweepstakes or contests. Another example is that we may use your information to process your registration with sites and apps. We may use your friends’ email addresses to send them information you requested we send them. We also use your information to process orders for you. We may also contact you if you have won a prize or promotion.

**We may use information to improve our products and services.** One of our goals is that you have a positive experience with our sites, apps, and products. Therefore, we may use your information to improve your experience with our sites, apps, and products. We might use your information to personalize your experience with us. We may use information you provide or that third-party partners give us to personalize your experience.

**We may use information for security and safety purposes.** We may use your information to help protect you, our sites and apps, our company, our customers, and our consumers.

**We may use information for marketing purposes.** For example, we might send you information about products, offers, features, or updates. We might also use your information to serve you ads about products and offers. Those ads may appear on third-party platforms which may include social media. These might be our own offers or products, or third-party offers or products we think you might find interesting. We may provide you with information through email or push notification.

**We may use information to get feedback from you about how we’re doing and for other transactional purposes.** We may contact you about this Notice or the Terms of Use posted to the sites or apps you are using. We may also communicate with you about a job application or your questions about our products or promotions.

**We may use information as the law allows us or as we may notify you.**

##### How we may share information we have collected

**We may share information within the PepsiCo family of companies and brands.** This includes current and future PepsiCo subsidiaries, affiliates, and joint venture partners. This also includes current brands such as Pepsi, Frito-Lay, Gatorade, and Quaker; and all future brands. For a list of PepsiCo brands, visit [https://www.pepsico.com/our-brands/creating-smiles/our-products](https://www.pepsico.com/our-brands/creating-smiles/our-products). We may also share information with third parties with which we have an ownership interest or commercial relationship, such as companies whose products we distribute.

**We may share information with third-party vendors.** We may share information with companies who serve as our vendors or third parties who perform services on our behalf. They may help us deliver products or services to you. For example, we may share information with companies who operate our sites and apps or who run our promotions.

**We may share information with select business partners.** For example, we may share information with joint promotion partners. If you register for a joint promotion, your information may be collected by both us and the third party. This might include retailers. Your information will be used by us as described in this Notice or by promotion partners as described in their policies.  

**We work with analytics and advertising partners.** Our online Services may use analytics, advertising and other third-party content or functionality through which our partners may collect internet and electronic network activity information, such as device and usage information. For additional information, please visit our [About Our Ads](https://www.pepsico.com/legal/about-our-ads) policy.

**We will share information if we think we must in order to comply with the law or to protect our company.** For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may share information if a government agency or investigatory body requests it. This includes United States and non-United States law enforcement or regulatory authorities. We may also share information if we are investigating potential fraud.

**We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business.** For example, if part of our business is sold we may include your information as part of that transaction.

**If there are additional reasons we may share information, we will describe those to you.**

##### You have certain choices about how we use your information

**You can opt out of email marketing.** To stop receiving promotional emails from us, follow the instructions in any promotional email message you get from us. If you opt out of getting marketing email messages, you may continue to receive non-marketing email messages from us where permitted by law.  

**You can control cookies and tracking tools.** To learn how to manage how we and our vendors use cookies and other tracking tools, and to read our [About Our Ads](https://www.pepsico.com/legal/about-our-ads) policy.

_Do-Not-Track Signals and Similar Mechanisms._ Some web browsers transmit "do-not-track" signals to websites. Because the standards for these signals are still under development, we currently do not take action in response to these signals.

**You can control tools on your mobile devices.** For example, you can turn off the GPS locator or push notifications on your phone. To modify the push notifications you get from our app, you can alter your preferences in your profile.

**You may have other choices under applicable state laws.** Depending on where you live, you may have certain additional rights, as described below. We only honor these rights where required by law.

* You may have a right to request to confirm whether or not we process your personal information as well as to access and receive a copy of the specific personal information we have collected about you in a portable format. 
* You may have a right to request deletion of your personal information. 
* You may have a right to request correction of any inaccurate personal information we hold about you.
* You may have the right to opt out of the sale, sharing or targeted advertising of personal information to third parties.
* In some circumstances, you may have the right to opt out of automated decision making and profiling, such as where it produces legal or other significant effects.
* You may have the right to opt-out of the processing (or limit the use) of your sensitive personal information.
* You have a right not to receive discriminatory treatment for exercising any of your rights described under this section.

These additional rights are subject to exceptions under applicable laws. For example, we may not be able to honor certain rights requests without taking reasonable steps to verify your identity.

If you would like to exercise these rights under applicable state privacy laws, you or your authorized agent have two options for doing so:

* **Call Us:** You may call us at our toll-free number, **1-833-548-0119**; or
* **Submit Through Our Portal:** You may submit your request through our [secure web portal](https://submit-irm.trustarc.com/services/validation/1d1278fc-851b-47d4-893d-c3b662f2425a).

We may reasonably verify your request by asking you to provide information to confirm your identity. This information may vary depending on your relationship with us. If you are a consumer in a jurisdiction that recognizes the ability to use an authorized agent and wish to contact us through an authorized agent, we may request evidence that you have provided such agent with power of attorney or that the agent otherwise has valid written authority to submit requests to exercise rights on your behalf. 

If you are in a jurisdiction that recognizes your ability to appeal a decision we have made in connection with your attempt to assert a right under applicable laws, you may submit a request to appeal through our [secure web portal](https://submit-irm.trustarc.com/services/validation/1d1278fc-851b-47d4-893d-c3b662f2425a).

Please provide the state that you are writing from, accompanied with information you may have regarding the matter you are appealing. If your jurisdiction allows you to file a complaint with the state’s Attorney General’s Office regarding any concerns with the result of your appeal request, you may do so by using their online properties.

**How we may sell or share your personal information**

Residents of certain states may also have the right to opt-out of the sale of personal information and the sharing of personal information for targeted advertising. We do not sell your information for money, but our Services may use analytics and advertising technologies, including those provided by advertising partners that use your personal information to serve you targeted advertising that is based on your activity across our Services and third-party websites, apps and services. 

We do not have actual knowledge that we sell or share the personal information of consumers under 16 years of age.  

If you do not wish for us to sell or share your personal information for targeted advertising purposes, you can opt out by submitting your request through [Your Privacy Choices](https://submit-irm.trustarc.com/services/validation/1d1278fc-851b-47d4-893d-c3b662f2425a). 

##### Retention of personal information 

We keep the categories of personal information described above for as long as is necessary for the purposes described in this Notice or otherwise authorized by law. This generally means holding the information for as long as one of the following apply:

* Your personal information is reasonably necessary to manage our operations, to manage your relationship with us, or to satisfy another purpose for which we collected the information;
* Your personal information is reasonably necessary to carry out a disclosed purpose that is reasonably compatible with the context in which the personal information was collected;
* The information is reasonably required to protect or defend our rights or property (which will generally relate to applicable laws that limit actions in a particular case); or
* We are otherwise required or permitted to keep your information by applicable laws or regulations.

##### Children's privacy

It is not our intention to collect personal information from children under age 13. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think that your child under 13 has given us information, you can contact us at [https://contact.pepsico.com/pepsico/contact-us](https://contact.pepsico.com/pepsico/contact-us) and we will take appropriate steps. You can also write to us at the address listed below. Please mark your inquiries “COPPA Information Request.” Parents, you can learn more about [how to protect children’s privacy online](https://consumer.ftc.gov/articles/protecting-your-childs-privacy-online).  

##### Biometric data

**We may collect Biometric Data.** PepsiCo may collect, store, and use biometric data from employees, consumers, or other individuals during the course of conducting PepsiCo’s operations and providing products or services.  PepsiCo will obtain written consent to collect, store, and use any biometric data, as required by law.

**What is biometric data?** Biometric data means data that consists of, or is derived from, biological information or physical characteristics unique to an individual that can be used to identify that individual (such as a fingerprint, handprint, retina or iris scan, voiceprint, or facial geometry scan).  

**Does PepsiCo share biometric data?** PepsiCo will not disclose or disseminate your biometric data to any third party unless it provides you notice and obtains your written consent to such disclosure or dissemination, or as required by law.

**How long does PepsiCo keep biometric data?** Unless otherwise required by an order from a court of competent jurisdiction or applicable law, PepsiCo will permanently destroy biometric data when the first of the following happens: (1) PepsiCo’s initial reason for collecting the biometric data is satisfied; or (2) within two years of an individual’s last interaction with PepsiCo.

**How does PepsiCo protect and store biometric data?** PepsiCo shall use a reasonable standard of care to store, transmit and protect from disclosure any biometric data collected from you.  

##### Security measures

We use various technical and organizational measures and mechanisms to secure our websites and apps. You should understand that no data storage system or transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secure.  

##### Our services are intended for a United States audience

If you are outside of the United States, please visit the site designated for you. You can find it by going to [PepsiCo.com/global-sites](https://www.pepsico.com/global-sites). If you live outside of the United States and choose to use this site or app, you understand that it is at your own risk. You also understand that your information will be sent to and stored in the United States. The United States may not afford the same level of protection as laws in your own country.  

##### We may link to other sites or apps or have third-party services and tools on our platform we don't control

We may link to or allow you to access the Services from third-party websites or platforms. Our sites and apps may also include third-party content that collects information. Third-party content may include tools like cookies and tracking technologies. These third parties may use your information for their own purposes. This may include behavioral advertising and analytic purposes. We do not control these third parties or their use of these technologies, so please read their privacy policies carefully.  

##### We may update this notice

From time to time, we may change this Notice. When we do, we will notify you of any material changes as required by law. This may include posting an updated copy here and updating the “Last Updated” date. Please check this Notice periodically for updates.  

##### California specific notices

**California “Shine the Light” Law**  

If you reside in California, you have the right to ask us one time per year for information about our disclosure, if any, of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. To make a request, please contact us at [https://contact.pepsico.com/pepsico/contact-us](https://contact.pepsico.com/pepsico/contact-us) or write to us at the address listed below. Indicate in your letter that you are a California resident making a “Shine the Light” inquiry. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than by the means specified in this section, if the request is not labeled or sent properly, or if the request does not have complete information.

**California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”)**

We have explained our privacy practices in full in the other sections of this Notice. In this section, we provide a list of categories of personal information, as set forth in the CCPA, that have been collected, disclosed for business purposes, shared for cross-context behavioral advertising, or sold for commercial purposes during the preceding 12 months, as well as certain other supplemental information. Some of these categories of personal information that we collect may include information that is considered sensitive under the CCPA.

Please see the other sections of this Notice for additional information about our practices and your rights. The personal information we collect about you may include information within the below noted categories of data. While the categories are as defined under California law, the disclosures below also apply to residents of other states as well.  

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Category of personal information** | **Explanation** |
| **Identifiers**, such as your name, street address, phone number, IP address, or email address | We may use this information to respond to your questions, to enable you to participate in our programs (including sweepstakes or contests), to process your registration with sites and apps, and for other business purposes. |
|     |     |
| **Commercial information**, such as a record of your purchases | We may use your information to provide you with products, to identify other products and offers that may be relevant to you, and for other business purposes. |
|     |     |
| **Biometric information**, such as voice recordings, images, and information about your physical activities that you provide | We use this information to provide you products and the Services and for our other business purposes, such as when we capture voice recordings as part of our customer support. For more information, please see our [biometric data](#biometricdata) section in this Notice, which includes additional descriptions of how we use, protect, and store biometric data. |
|     |     |
| **Internet and electronic network activity information**, such as information about your interactions with our Services | We may use this information to improve our Services, to better understand the visitors who come to our Services and what content is of interest to them, and for other business purposes. |
|     |     |
| **Precise geolocation information**, using technologies such as GPS or Wi-Fi | We may use this information to improve the quality, security, and relevance of our Services to our visitors and for other business purposes. |
|     |     |
| **Other electronic information**, including information you post in a public space on our site (such as videos or photos) | We may use this information to provide the services you ask for on our Services, as part of sweepstakes or other competitions, and for other business purposes. |
|     |     |
| **Inferences** about you | We may use this information to personalize your experience with us, and for other business purposes. |
|     |     |
| **Characteristics of protected classifications under applicable state or federal law**, such as your gender | We may use this information for our equal employment opportunity program, and for other business purposes. |

View [our statistics on CCPA requests](https://policy.pepsico.com/privacystats.htm).

As discussed in the other sections of this Notice, we collect these categories of information from you, through our interactions with you and others, and from third-parties, and we disclose these categories of personal information within the PepsiCo family of companies and brands, to business partners and third-party vendors that provide us hosting, advertising, and other services, to advertising and analytics partners, and as needed to comply with legal process.

Your personal information may also be disclosed to third-parties with whom you interact and third parties that you direct us to disclose your information to through our Services. We may also disclose personal information with third-parties in various additional ways, as described elsewhere in this Notice. 

In California, you may have certain additional rights under applicable law, in addition to your rights to access, correct, and delete your personal information as described above. In California, you also may have:

* The right to request other information about our data processing practices, including the categories of personal information that have been collected about you; the categories of sources from which personal information are collected; our business or commercial purpose for collecting, using, disclosing, selling or sharing personal information; the categories of third parties with whom we disclose, sell or share personal information; and the categories of personal information we have disclosed, sold or shared about you for a business purpose.
* The right to direct us to limit the use and disclosure of your sensitive personal information to certain uses and disclosures, such as those that are reasonably necessary to provide our goods and services or as needed to ensure security and integrity, to prevent fraud or illegal activity, or for physical safety.

If you would like to exercise these rights under applicable state privacy laws, you or your authorized agent have two options for doing so:

* **Call us:** You may call us at our toll-free number, **1-833-548-0119**; or
* **Submit through our portal:** You may submit your request through our [secure web portal](https://submit-irm.trustarc.com/services/validation/1d1278fc-851b-47d4-893d-c3b662f2425a).

_Sale or Sharing._ Over the past 12 months, we have worked with advertising partners who assist us with our targeted advertising activities, who may have had access to identifiers, Internet and other electronic network activity information, geolocation data, and other personal information.

To the extent we collect precise geolocation information for purposes of performing a Service you have requested, we may be deemed to be collecting data that is “sensitive” under California law. Our use of this data for performing a Service you have requested is consistent with the permitted business purposes in California Civil Code § 1798.100 et seq. and implementing regulations.

If you do not wish for us to sell or share your personal information for targeted advertising purposes, you can opt out by submitting your request through [Your Privacy Choices](https://submit-irm.trustarc.com/services/validation/1d1278fc-851b-47d4-893d-c3b662f2425a). 

**Financial Incentives** 

We offer PepsiCo Tasty Rewards (“PTR”), a rewards program that provides benefits such as rewards points and discounts to those who opt in by choosing to participate, and other similar promotional programs. Participation in these programs may require you to provide some personal information, such as name, date of birth, address, telephone number, and email address, which we use to operate the program, including to send you offers and discounts, and for the other purposes described in this Notice. Additional information related to PTR is available [on TastyRewards.com](https://www.tastyrewards.com/en-us). For the full terms and conditions, please review the terms and conditions for the applicable program.  

The incentives associated with PTR and similar programs are designed to reward loyal customers based on the volume of products they purchase from us rather than the value of your personal information. Based on our reasonable and good faith estimate, we receive value from PTR in increased loyalty and purchases.   

You have the right to withdraw from the financial incentive at any time by canceling your participation in PTR or similar programs by contacting us as indicated below.

**Feel free to contact us if you have more questions**

If you have questions about this Notice or our data practices, please click on the “General question” box located at [https://contact.pepsico.com/pepsico/contact-us](https://contact.pepsico.com/pepsico/contact-us) to submit your question. You can also write to us or call us at:  

PepsiCo, Inc.  
Attn: Consumer Relations  
700 Anderson Hill Road  
Purchase, NY 10577  
1-800-433-2652  

Clear

Close 1-Atoms/icons/close@3x

[](https://www.pepsico.com/)Back to top

© PepsiCo 20 [Terms of Use](https://www.pepsico.com/legal/terms-of-use) [Privacy Policy](https://www.pepsico.com/legal/privacy) [Accessibility Statement](https://www.pepsico.com/legal/accessibility-statement) [About Our Ads](https://www.pepsico.com/legal/about-our-ads) [Modern Slavery Statement](https://www.pepsico.com/docs/default-source/sustainability-and-esg-topics/2023-pepsico-modern-slavery-and-human-trafficking-statement.pdf)
